{
    "id": "89676242c24046ca8f4d636ae20a9aca",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We all trust people ………………….. speak the truth.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bff4f750d5c848d7b4cc9b7330e861f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………. does his best shall be rewarded.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dd755f1bb4e44f84a25476828f511fd4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t understand …………………… you mean.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4bfd6d22297d48a89210f5643feba23a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has gone to Bangalore, ………………… is her birth place.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "239876cf75d6444e8ad2e7a27e36b565"
        },
        {
            "question": "You should learn to give away ……………………… you do not need.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fdcb4f9b63d1474cb3b6bbe2484867e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is no one ……………………… has not lost a dear one.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a4cf53a3a010415295ac6877c8424ba2"
        },
        {
            "question": "You get …………………….. you deserve.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f3fa4cd9c0db44d69f903fd229883538"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a person ……………………. you can trust.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4011b6dc32a646458412fbdb9d87bdde"
        },
        {
            "question": "The letter ……………………. he sent never reached me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "60023582c5a84999b28ee820013c54f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………………… treats others with kindness will be treated with kindness.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dcbdbeb9e729466195ce3d0081f92fdc"
        }
    ]
}